# **AARON MEREDITH**

**9** 4/4 Douglas st, Mount Cook, Wellington, New Zealand

□ aaron@aaron-m.co.nz

**\** 02040438188

# **OBJECTIVE**

I'm looking for full time work in the IT and telecommunications industry.

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

Programming for me is not just a career, its also a creative outlet. I love learning and experimenting with new technologies and techniques. This helps me enhance my professional skills which can be used at work or at leisure.

By visiting my website aaron-m.co.nz you can find various projects that I have worked on.

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### **MEA Mobile**

Wellington, New Zealand Aug 2012 - Sep 2017

# Web Developer

Mea Mobile is a full service that designs and develops for most forms of digital devices and physical media.

My focus was websites and web applications, either as standalone projects built up from scratch or to supplement mobile applications in the form of APIs or Sales Websites.

Over the Last 5 years at MEA Mobile I have had considerable experience with frameworks such as Symfony, Laravel, Wordpress, SilverStripe and more recently getting into ReactJS and Angular.

Directly working with clients to help understand what they want.

Working with clients and client feedback during the development phase.

Working with clients on continued support and maintenance agreements to implement features and squash bugs.

Developing and maintaining the front end and back end functionality of websites.

Developing and maintaining API's.

Writing cross-browser, responsive, compliant HTML5, CSS3 & JavaScript

Using tools that include Gulp, Webpack, Sass, Composer.

Managing Linux based Amazon Ec2 servers for hosting.

Designing buttons, banners, logos for websites.

# Rimuhosting

Cambridge, New Zealand Nov 2009 - Aug 2012

## Web Developer / Designer

This was a full time paid internship during the summer break of the second year of study. After the internship I took on a full time position.

Frontend development which included Java, JSP, Servlets, Javascript, CSS

# **QUALIFICATIONS**

# University of Waikato

Hamilton, New Zealand 2008 - 2010

## Bethlehem College

Tauranga, New Zealand 2004

# Bachelor of Computing and Mathematical Sciences

Completed 2 out of 4 years and left to pursue a full time position after completing a summer internship at Rimuhosting.

## NCEA Level 2

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- PHP Symfony, Laravel, Silverstripe, Wordpress
- CSS Sass, Less
- MySQL
- Illustrator / Inkscape

- Javascript Gulp, WebPack, Nodejs, Angular, Vuejs, React
- AWS & Linux systems Bash, Python
- PhotoShop
- HTML

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

#### Positive Attitude

#### Willing to learn

Open to learning the best tools to complete a task. In the past this has included learning Java, Laravel, Symfony and React.

#### Communication

Engaging with clients and co-workers to discuss problems and find solutions.

#### **INTERESTS**

- Experimental Programming
- Craft Beer
- Designing Graphics

- Gaming
- Badminton

# **REFEREES**

# **Rodney Macfarlane**

Employer - MEA Mobile

☑ rod@we-are-mea.com

**C** 021 729 438

# Fiona D'Silva Moiyadi

Business Development Manager - MEA Mobile

**\** 0212579011

#### **Kat Cox**

Senior Digital Producer - Young + Shand

**C** 021317341

# Rey Benher

Web Team Manager - MEA Mobile

☑ r.benher@we-are-mea.com

**\** 021 079 0899